We really need to get first place in that Beat Contest
We’ll win it for sure, bro, you’re just anxious.
I don't even have any money left. My drumstick is also completely spoiled.
- There, there.
We have Pete. He's our rich guy.
We’ll get you a new one, don’t worry.
You swear?
Of course.
- Yes!
Bro...
Ah! Not you too!
So cunning, I’ll will remember this.
-Let’s move, guys.
There’s something stuck on your hair. I’ll buy a guitar pick for you.
No.
Okay?
No. You’ll get me an ugly pick.
No, I know a nice one, Dave.
I don’t care.
Whose guitar did you bring home this time?
You should concentrate on your studies.
Ah, don’t worry, mom.
You’re neglecting your studies.
I’m definitely gonna pass the exam.
All you think about is music.
Is that chicken?
Listen to what I’m saying. How will you manage to find a job?
Look, mom. I know, I know.
How will you have the confidence to find a wife?
Ah! I’m going to study.
Damn, it’s my restricted day for driving.
How much is it till PUC?
It’s Rs.600 till the main gate.
Aish!
Get out. Don’t ever let me see you again. I can find plenty of other women.
Uh, can you go for Rs.500?
Fine, I’ll do it.
Thank you so much.
Sir, can I get a ride?
Where are you headed?
E, oh, you can use this. I can just hail another one.
Sir, how much is it for Khatla?
That’ll be Rs.300.
Can you drop me for Rs.150?
Young lady, that won’t be possible, you’ll have to wait for another taxi.
Here, I’ll pay for you.
Thank you so much. I’ll pay you back. Sir, Khatla.
What?
Are you on your way?
I’m studying, you should try it sometimes.
Look, we’re all waiting for you to start the jam. See? Get here fast.
I’m going to study.
The exam is still far away and the Beat Contest is just a few days away.
You’re the one to kept on stressing that it’s important.
Get here fast. Guess we’ll see which is more important to you. Come. I’m hanging up.
Hello
Hi... oh, it’s you? Come, have a seat.
How are you?
Yes, I’m good.
I’m Zodina.
Oh, by the way, here, from the other day....
There’s no need to-
No... don’t say no...
- I’m serious, you don’t have to pay me back.
No, I feel bad... It’s such a huge amount.
Can you please take it so that I can feel better?
Oye, oye, oye. What are you gonna order?
Whatever you guys like. Uh, Dave, this is my friend…
Betsie
Betsie? Okay. I’m Dave.
Oh, did you write this? May I read it? You allow it, right?
You allow it, right?
- Go ahead...
Wow, You write songs?
Yeah, I occasionally write.
Mm! Do you make music as well?
I... kind of make it... I guess...
You know, we have a band, and if its okay with you, can you send Zodina your demo? Please?
Okay, I’ll send it to him.
Yes, you’re so nice.
Uh, Excuse me, would you like to place your order?
Wait, it’s the other table.
Send it to him, okay? I trust you.
He must have thought that we’ve known each other. I’m so sorry.
- That’s okay.
That’s okay.
Umm, while we’re at it, let’s exchange phone numbers and I’ll call you later?
Umm.
Yes! Thank you. I’ll get going then. Buh-bye.
Buh- bye.
You came home so late, I’ve been looking forward to eating the food you have prepared.
I made myself free since you’re back home anyway.
Do you want to have dinner now?
No, not now. I’ll have it later.
Big sis.
Hmm?
Boys from our locality keep on pestering me after they know about your separation.
They’d say something stupid like “When can we start courting your sister because I want to introduce her to my friend who is divorced.”
Or something like, “If I’m unmarried, or if I was still single, I wouldn’t mind courting her.”
It’s so stupid and so annoying. Men who talk excessively are not reliable sources of advice.
Ah! I don’t care so let them say whatever they want.
These men talk endlessly even on social media.
They are often the most opinionated, even on topics related to women.
- Hello?
And the same applies to issues related to men too.
Oh, really? I’ll be so grateful if it is possible. I’m so glad.
All right.
Oh my! You’re so crazy!
Who was it?
That was Kimi. The thing is… uh… I was thinking of staying over at Kimi’s house for the week.
Hmph!
Ahoy! Let’s start.
Let’s start.
We have just one week left to practice for the beat contest so let’s give it our all.
Beth,
Mm?
I have to leave early since our storekeeper is sick.
Is that so?
-  You can make whatever you want.
Ah, don’t worry about me, I’ll be all right.
By the way, bring home a smoked pork, let’s have it for dinner.
Okay… I’ll be leaving now. Buh- bye.
Buh-bye.
Beth, I left my key on my dressing table, can you throw it from the window?
Zoa, where are you going? You’ve got quite a handful.
I’m heading for my class.
Oh? With the guitar?
Yeah, we’re planning to jam right after the classes.
- Kim!
What are you doing here?
I’m staying over at Kimi’s house for a while. What about you?
This is my house.
Oh, you guys know each other?
Yeah, we do. I’ll come over some day, okay?
- Mm.
Yes, buh- bye.
Were you feeling lonely today?
Not at all. I enjoy having some time to myself so I’m pretty okay.
I’m worried about you.
I’m scared you’ll make bad decisions because of your broken heart.
It’s just so hard to wrap my head around it.
How I have to deal with it, my family... ah… my mind is blank for now.
You need to forget your past and look towards the future.
As time passes, you'll gradually heal and move on from this.
I guess I’ve become something I’ve never even dreamt for myself… a divorcee.
I don’t know how to explain it, it’s so weird.
Being a divorcee doesn’t have to shape how you live.
Be the Betsie that you’ve always been.
Be the Betsie that your family, your friends and everyone else loves. Don’t bother yourself with the rest.
I know I don’t understand the amount of pain you’re going through but I understand that you’re hurting.
It’ll get better, right?
It will.
Mhm.
Shall we go to bed? I’m super sleepy. But I’ll sleep beside you, okay?
Oh, by the way, my order from Online Mizoram will arrive tomorrow. Receive that for me, okay?
Mhm.
Bro, can you tell me Rinkimi’s address?
It’s this building here but I think she has left for her shop.
Her order has arrived.
I’ll just receive it on her behalf?
That’ll be great.
Here, Kimi’s package.
Oh, thank you. I’ll give it to her.
By the way, I made the demo.
Is that so? Then… what’s your plan for tomorrow?
Umm… I don’t know… why?
We’re going to perform at the Beat Contest. Mind coming to watch?
I’ll let you know tomorrow?
Okay, bye.
Hi! You guys were amazing.
I’m glad you could make it.
Uh, sorry for disturbing you all. You’re the Hangout Boys, right?
Yes. That’s us.
E… You are such great singers and your performance was amazing. Let me shake hands you.
Um… I’m John. This is my business card with my details and my phone number. Contact me and we’ll find a way to work together.
Okay. Thank you so much.
- Have a great day.
Where? Let me have a look.
Oh, my! This is MN Records.
Dave, have you heard of them?
- Its among the biggest record labels.
I think that guy is the owner.
I know.
Shall we go?
Let’s go. Come.
See? I told you, you guys did well. He knows how good you all are so he approached you.
It’s only because you came and watched us.
Are you going to stay for a while at Kimi’s place?
I was planning on going home this evening.
Then… let’s go to the café tomorrow?
I might not be available tomorrow; I plan to stay home and keep my sister company.
Okay. Bye-bye.
- Buh-bye.
Zodin, we’ll talk later about the café.
Mm! We may not be the winners but 2nd place isn’t that bad, right, MK?
Mmm. And the contract?
The contract, yeah, we might have a chance to have a professional contract.
Good, good. That’s good.
But, see, if we sign the contract, we’ll have to really-
Hey, Pete, now’s not the time for that.
Come, it’s the time to enjoy.
Let’s enjoy it. Let’s enjoy it. Let’s go!
Bro, let me tell you, I love her a lot. I really love her.
And she called me last night. I didn’t answer but I really wanted to.
Tell me, what’s going on between you and Betsie?
We can tell that you actually like her from the way you act.
That’s absurd! We’re just starting to know each other.
I’m serious. Don’t try to hide it.
It’s quite obvious from your actions, Zodin.
Huh!
When you had a crush, who was the first one to notice it?
It was me.
Even when you had a crush on a girl in class 10, who was the first one to know it? Huh?
I read you like a book, bro. I’m serious, I know you so well and I know you like her.
You’re so a annoying. Anyway, what do you think of her?
Married women are not my type.
If you like her, you have my full support.
I think I’m starting to really like Betsie.
We met by coincidence and what if I’m destined to be with her?
I know so many people who broke up who thought they were destined to be together.
If the two of you truly like each other, go pay the bride price now.
You are so drunk.
Ah… bro. I speak nothing but the truth. My only problem is that I’m so smart.
You just don’t understand.
Such nonsense.
On a serious note, Zodin, you have to think about yourself. Once you lift yourself higher, girls will come. Definitely.
You are so wasted.
Zodin, look up at the sky.
It has no limit.
The stars will know of our story.
I’m telling you
The Sky is Ours.
Oh, you were able to make it.
Come sit, come sit. Feel free to pull the chairs.
Oh, you guys seem to run a little late.
We stayed up late last night. We’re so sorry.
- I understand.
All right, anyway, we have drafted your contract,
Read it carefully, everything that you need to know, like how much you’re getting paid and what we expect from you,
Everything has been clearly stated, read it thoroughly and if you can sign it…
We’ll sign it.
You’re ready to sign? This is great news.
Just sign under each of your names.
Are you all excited?
All: Yes, we are.
You will become a global sensation.
Finally, I welcome you all to MN Records. Let’s shake hands.
Do you want to see your new studio?
Yeah.
- Yes,
You want to see it now? Follow me.
This is it.
Come in, come in.
This is so amazing!
Woah!
How is it? Is it to your liking?
Sir, this is more than what we have imagined.
Oh, really? Glad to hear that.
So, for your first task… hehe
Dave.
Uh, hehe, for your first task, come up with an original song
and we’ll try to shoot the music video as soon as possible.
But will you be able to come up with-
Sir, we’ll be able to make it.
You can?
Mm, we can.
You sure?
Sure.
If that’s the case then there’s nothing to be worried about.
Now that you have a new studio, make good use of it. I’ll be on my way.
All: Okay, thank you so much.
All: Yes!
This is so beautiful.
Woo! That’s nice!
Ah! I’m so annoyed. Nothing’s entering my head.
What are we gonna do now? You blankly said that we’ll do it.
We’ve already said yes so we have to go through with it now. Think.
Ah! My brain is empty right now.
Maybe we need to eat first.
Dude! You’re such a waste.
I would have finished writing the song if I were Taylor Swift.
But then again, I’m not.
Oh, wait! wait!
Has Betsie sent you her demo?
Oh, right!
Play the song, it might give us ideas.
If I know what was in your heart
I wouldn’t have given you my everything
All the tears that I have cried…
Wow!
Wouldn’t have been in vain…
We can definitely make a good arrangement with this.
Come, let’s follow along these lines.
Oh my! Betsie, how are you? We hardly see each other!
I’m good. How are you?
Mm, I’m good. I heard about what happened to you…
I’m so sad, to be divorced at such a young age… I felt so bad for you…
Did I keep you waiting?
Not at all.
You have to come with me.
I’ll have to go, bye, Nunu.
Where are we going?
You’ll see.
Guys, Betsie.
Yes! Come, sit here.
What’s going on? Huh?
Beth, we listened to your song and we love it.
Are you serious?
We want you to be our band songwriter.
This is ridiculous! What-
No, our manager expects a new song from us and none of us are able to write anything.
Even Pete said ‘wow’ to your song.
As much as I’m glad… I think this is too sudden…
All right, then, can you give us permission to sing your demo?
Umm…
Let me finish writing it and if you like it, you can use it.
Pete and Dave : Yes!
You guys have to sing it really well though.
Don’t worry, we have Zodina.
We will be so grateful, lalthiamtheinu! I need to get at least one girl with your song.
Hello?
Hello, Betsie, you were done writing so quick.
Yeah, I feel that it’s better to just finish it while it’s in your head.
That’s good.
We’re really thankful.
It’s no big deal.
Are you sure you really don’t want the money?
Uh, no... just treat me a coffee later.
Will treat you for sure.
All right, buh-bye.
Bye...
Without time wasted on you
I finally heal from all the pain
I know you’ve always denied our love
My foolish heart was scared of losing you
And now it’s getting late, your time’s run out
There’s no use in regretting
You never held me close in your heart
If I knew what was in your heart
I wouldn’t have given you my everything
All the tears that I have cried wouldn’t be in vain…
And now you don’t deserve my forgiveness, it’s out of reach for you
It won’t matter if you kneel, the sky won’t answer
Oh, it won’t matter…
Secondhand Serenade – Fall for you
For our new music video and Betsie.
- Wow! Yes!
It’s gonna be yumm!
Let’s grill this.
We’ll grill this first.
It’s so hot!
- Oh yeah, the sausage...
- Can you get the frying pan?
-Okay, where is it?
It will take a while.
Let’s play truth or dare.
Hmm?
Truth or dare. Up for it?
Let’s do it.
Guys, Let’s play truth or dare, you’re all in?
Ah…
- Let’s do it..
Fine, let’s do it
- Yes.
Whoever can’t do the challenge has to chuck the beer.
- Dave, spin.
I won’t join in, I don’t feel too well.
Ah, then, we’ll flick your forehead instead.
Hey!
Come on, let’s start!
I’ll spin the bottle.
-Go ahead.
Ehh! Yes!
- Aah!
This one’s mine.
Ah! Truth or dare?
Truth.
When are you going to ask out Betsie?
Ah!
Can’t change it.
- Dare.
No, can’t change it.
Dare. Dare, Dare.
- Can’t change it.
I’ll sing instead.
Nah, that’s cheating.
Fine, then, sing.
Watching the sun setting
Makes me lonely
I felt the breeze of the wind
And it makes me miss you more
I can't stop seeing your ghost in my dreams
You'll never grow old in my heart.
All the way to Europe?
Mm… I’ve always wanted to go there, like, there are so many places I want to photograph. So many...
Like Big Ben and Buckingham Palace?
Those are all in England!
England is still a part of Europe.
It is, but I mean, I want to visit places like…
Um, I mean, rather than the city, I prefer the countryside, the little cottages, their farmlands… I want to visit those places.
With a huge lake.
- Mmm.
Take me there one day, okay?
I’ll definitely take you.
Promise?
- Yes.
Tonight has been great.
I’m glad you came along.
I’m the one who is glad, I needed to go out. I’m glad you invited me.
Speaking of which, you might find it uncomfortable to talk about it…
What happened the day we met?
What of it?
- It’s okay if you don’t want to talk about it.
Um… it's not that I don’t want to talk about it…
The person I fought with that day is my ex-husband, Zuala.
We used to stay there… and we were married for two years…
But… yeah, I have my own faults… it was so hard to tolerate it…
But I’m trying to forget about it.
Besides, rather than being the Betsie whose husband beats her up, I want to be just me, just Betsie.
What’s wrong with him? He’s taking so long.
We’re going to be late, try calling him.
This is too much.
Hello, hello.
Ah, he’s finally here.
What took you so long!
What’s the meaning of this?
I asked John to let Betsie join us.
And?
He agreed.
Betsie is coming with us?
Mka and Pete: Yes!
Did I give you permission to come along?
Let’s go, let’s go!
You’re not my boss.
You guys did so great!
Ah! Thank you, thank you.
How was it?
It was awesome
Huh!
You’re all tired.
It’s John.
Hello, hello! You were able to perform well?
Yes, sir.
That’s great. That’s great.
I really wanted to come but I couldn’t make it.
Really wished I could join as well. So, how’s Bangkok? Did you face any problems?
No, we didn’t. We’re enjoying it, sir.
Is Betsie enjoying it?
I love it, thank you so much, John.
Glad you’re enjoying it.
Take proper rest tonight since you’re coming home tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Okay, then, good night.
Good night.
We don’t need to sleep early. We’ll go out.
We have an early flight tomorrow.
We’re not gonna- you’re just worried, we won’t be late.
We’ll be late.
We’re not going to be late.
Drink fast. I want to sleep early.
Even I want to try the street food.
Oh my God!
There’s no point in staying indoors while travelling. You have to go out.
I’m not in the mood to explore…
Don’t be a wuss.
I’m exhausted!
Get up, hey!
- I don’t wan to!
Just get up!
Tonight is the only chance we’ll get to go out.
Where did this guy go off to?
Oh, no! I forgot my wallet. I’ll go trace my steps.
We’ll wait for you at the hotel.
Okay, okay. I’ll search for him as well.
Hi.
So… pretty face got a name?
Olivia.
Olivia.? That’s a beautiful name.
Thank you.
So, where you from?
I’m from Brazil.
Brazil? how do you say ‘you have beautiful eyes’ in Portuguese?
Olhos bonitos (beautiful eyes)
Obrigado (thank you)
Can I buy you a drink?
Umm... Sure.
What kind of drink do you want?
What about cocktail?
Cocktail? Can we get two margaritas… for me and this angel.
Tonight has been so fun.
Can you call him?
I’ve called thrice.
Damn frustrating.
Should we just tell John? What should we do?
Ah! He’s our friend, there’s no need to tell him.
The call can get through but he can’t pick up.
Look there… he is so damn buzzed.
Hello, hello! Hello!
Pete! Where did you go?
- I’m so drunk!
I don’t even remember
Where did you go?
I went to club… and the girl I was dancing with…
Turned out to be a guy!
Na! So stupid!
Come, let’s go up.
But hey!
Yeah, bro
Zodin, you can’t tell anyone. You hear me? Even you, MK!
Not to a single soul.
Where did you go last night?
Do you even know when our flight is scheduled?
What if we had missed our flight because of you? What would you do?
Are you gonna pay for our tickets? You’ll pay?
Mmm
- You’ll pay?
Fuckin get ready.
What did you get me?
Nothing, I told you I’m broke.
You could’ve gotten me at least one thing.
You spent so much time with your boyfriend that you forgot about me.
Here! Always ready to sulk.
Yes! Thank you!
I’ll put it on now.
Mmm.
Does it look good?
What happened?
- Get me a glass of water.
Here, drink it.
I’ll get more water, okay?
Come, lay down.
No, I’m okay now. It was just a small ache.
Lay down here… and keep your legs straight.
- I’m okay.
I’ll be okay…
- 00:45:33:16
I’ll get more water, okay?
Mm.
I’ll bring a paracetamol too.
The call is not getting through?
He isn’t picking up…
It’s so annoying.
Oh, sir, how are you?
How have you been?
- I’m John.
You guys are good? Able to reach home safe? Where’s Dave?
Our calls can’t get through.
Oh… okay…
E… yeah, since I couldn’t join you… you guys faced any trouble?
No trouble at all, sir. We’re really grateful.
Did you all enjoy the trip?
Just that Pete can’t different between a girl and a boy, apart from that, no trouble at all.
Oh... that’s horrible.
Zodina was just kidding.
Yeah, you have to be careful in Thailand…They all look the same so unless you touch it, you can’t differentiate them anymore.
So, Zodin, did Betsie enjoy the trip? We guys would have stuck together like glue.
They say that falling for a married woman hits differently.
On a serious note, the reason I urgently asked you guys here is because we’re nearing the end of the year and there are going to be quite a lot of events.
You will be fairly busy and our biggest challenge and our main goal will be winning the Thazual Award
Even if you don’t have much free time, just remember that all this hard work will pay off in the end, it won’t go in vain.
And if I’m not mistaken, day after tomo-
Hello!
E... you... come over here.
Mm. here, let’s shake hands as well.
Hold on. E… you still reek of Bangkok.
Huh… just go and sit down. Ask your friends all the important things I said. Tell Dave what we have discussed.
Yes.
As I was saying, day after tomorrow, which is on the 9th, you will have a gig
You might be tired to practice immediately but you’ll have to start from tomorrow.
Uh, Dave will also drink lots of water
- Yes!
You’ll be up for it tomorrow, right?
- I will!
Ah, that’s good.
They flew home yesterday.
Oh, really?
Mm. Go look at Mka’s story.
Gosh, I like Pete so much, and he’s so cool!
Zodina is much better.
Mka is so adorable.
Who should I like? Pete or Dave? But I heard Dave is such a womanizer.
See? Rin, you have a chance.
Go away! I heard people say that Zodina’s girlfriend has been married before.
Is that true?
It’s such a pity, Zodina is still so young.
She went to Thailand with them, like, what did she even do?
Exactly.
Get divorced, he might like you back.
Should I? He might like me cuz of it.
He obviously will like you!
Bro, did Betsie come today?
Uh, the girl with the short hair?
She came but she left really early.
Zodin, can my friend take a photo with you?
I’m so sorry but I am in a bit of a hurry.
Oh, okay.
Come in.
Is anyone home?
Oh, Zodin, where’s my sister?
She’s not at home?
No, she left in the morning. I thought you went out together.
No… didn’t go out together.
Have a seat. I’ll go make tea.
Okay. Let’s have tea.
Did you enjoy the trip?
It was good.
What did you get me?
Nothing, brought back your sister.
I really wanted to come as well.
Did you talk to Pete for me?
Pete? He doesn’t care about these things. You have to act first.
I’m too shy to talk to him!
You shouldn’t be shy!
I thought you’d say something to him at least.
I’ll tell him if I don’t forget it.
- Mmm.
Mm. I’ll go take care of the laundry.
Bah!
Oi! You scared me!
Hello
Hi!
Where did you go today?
To the café.
I came to the café but you weren’t there.
I didn’t feel good so I went home early.
If that’s the case then you should’ve told me…
You didn’t even pick up the call.
You feel better now?
Yeah, much better.
Then… have dinner at my place?
Mom’s away, travelling and… I’ll be the chef for the night.
I’m scared to taste your cooking
Fine, don’t come and eat.
Hey, I was kidding! Where are you even going?
What are you doing here, Mk?
My family told me to buy some groceries. What about you?
I’m having Betsie over for dinner
That’s gonna be fun.
Don’t forget the jam on Friday.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you. Mk, take your salary on your way out.
Hi
- Hello
Come on in.
You look amazing.
That’s so nice of you to say.
Come.
Let me get the chair for you.
Are you hungry?
Not much, I ate something earlier.
Very well then.
I was kidding!
So what are you making?
You’ll know it once I finish making it.
Are you actually pissed off?
No I’m not.
You are!
You’re so irritating!
Tom or Jerry?
Jerry.
I prefer Tom
Hmph! Just because I don’t choose him.
Jerry always disturbs Tom while he is minding his own business, and Jerry always wins in the end.
Don’t you feel sad for him?
Just think about it, all that Jerry does is search for food
And Tom always bullies him.
I want to be like Tom and Jerry
Why?
Even though they always fight, they never leave each other.
I’ll be Jerry and you’ll be Tom.
I like spending time together like this.
We hardly have time to spend with each other.
You missed me a lot then?
Of course I do. You don’t miss me?
Did I say I don’t? Huh?
All good?
I’ll just go to the bathroom.
Hello?
Mm... I’ll come over. Hmm... okay buh-bye.
Guys, I have to move.
Where the heck are you going? Our gig is tomorrow!
Who cares? We already know the song, won’t make mistakes.
I’m in a hurry and it’s important, so I’ll leave. Goodnight!
Ah! He killed my spirit.
We’ll wrap it up for now?
We’ll come to practice early tomorrow for the rehearsal, that okay Mk?
Fine, let’s do that.
Look at Lilac
She’s singing so great tonight.
Le, le, le, le, are we ready?
Why do we look so gloomy? And where is Dave?
He’s on his way, John.
He is just on his way? What’s going on!?
Uh… he’s stuck in traffic.
There’s no traffic jam at this hour.
Mm. I’ll cancel the gig if he doesn’t reach here within 20 minutes. Call him right now!
Call him!
He’s finally here.
What took you so long?
Guys.
Are you drunk!?
I’m here anyway!
Sober up! We’re going to start.
Always shouting at me whenever--
I’m haven’t shouted at you enough! Look at yourself!
Why do I have to look at myself? Look at yourself instead!
I swear I’ll-
They’ve called our name, let’s go first.
Without time wasted on you
I finally heal from all the pain
I know you’ve always denied our love
My foolish heart was scared of losing you
And now it’s getting late, your time’s run out
There’s no use in regretting
You never held me close in your heart
If I knew what-
Continue playing the song, do it.
Look at Dave!
He looks so drunk.
Dave!
-
Dave! The fuck is going with you?
It was a minor mistake. Sorry.
You embarrassed us out there!
I said I’m sorry…
You’re sorry? How many times have I told you to fix yourself?
As if you have never done anything wrong. Don’t think you’re at the top just because you’re the band leader.
How dare you!
Hey! Stop it!
Let me go!
Enough, enough.
Let me tell you. You’re not going to find a better guitarist than me for this band.
Hey! Hey!
What the hell is wrong with you guys?
Do you have no shame? There are so many people around!
Making such a huge ruckus.
- Dave, Dave, Dave!
Run after Dave. Go! Run after him now!
You can’t get through to Dave?
Look at this.
You know that you have breached the contract right?
We’re sorry, John.
Saying sorry doesn’t fix anything.
Think about it. You were going to be at the peak of your fame.
-
Mistakes can cause dire consequences.
We’re coming up with a new song, we’ll recover.
You’ll have a new song?
But what of Dave?
What did John say?
He made me sign a settlement agreement for the breach of contract.
He gave us time to get everything sorted out but we can’t do it without Dave.
Where’s Pete?
His family called him so he left.
You’re not gonna go home yet?
Mm. I’ll stay for a while.
Zo, does this mean we have disbanded?
I’ve never mentioned this, but, I never had anything…
the things I’ve said about my parents, they were all lies
I never got a chance to see them…
My uncle took care of me… I make up these lies to fit in.
Then I get to have such great friends in college
And now, you guys are not just friends, you’re my only family,
I’m losing the only family that I have.
You go ahead, I’ll stay for a while.
How are you, Betsie?
What do you want?
Don’t you miss me at all? We haven’t spoken for ages.
We have been separated for so long now, Zuala, why do you continue bothering me?
We haven’t even signed our divorce papers yet. You’re still my wife by law.
I’d rather choose death than be your wife.
Do you think you’ll be able to honour vows when you can’t even honour ours?
And you’re saying that you’re dating a celebrity.
Do you know how others are talking behind your back?
People are gossiping about the fact that we’re separated.
I do not owe you anything. Being married to you was worse than hell.
Zodina is a much better man than you’ll ever be.
And you? You’re nothing. You’re nothing but a man who beats his wife up.
Marrying you was the worst decision of my life.
I’d rather stay a divorcee than bring you back into my life.
Damn bitch.
Slap me if you dare! Do you think I’m still scared of you? I’m not intimidated by you in the least.
I’m not even your wife anymore, don’t ever show your face in front of me again.
Feli, where is your sister?
She’s upstairs. You can go upstairs.
Zo…
Where were you today? Why didn’t you answer my calls?
I went to the bazaar.
Who is this man?
Zo, it’s not what you think-
Who is he?
Who!?
That’s Zuala, my ex-husband.
Beth, you want to go back to your husband after all that we’ve been through?
I’m telling you the truth, there is nothing between us.
I want to believe you. I really want to believe you, but I can’t.
Don’t say whatever you want based on assumptions.
Then tell me what I don’t know!
All those times we’ve spent together, were they lies?
Stop talking, Zodinsang!
There is nothing between me and Zuala.
I faced him with  every strength I had only because of you.
You should have told me that you met him. You should’ve told me!
I’ve always wanted to tell you! There is nothing between me and him.
I didn’t want my past to interfere with us, so I wanted to resolve things on my own… now I’ve resolved it, it’s done.
Beth…
Zo, please leave me alone for now.
Sis, all good?
Good. I’m going to my room, don’t disturb me.
Zodin, what are you doing?
My sister’s in her room, go.
The blue moon and the stars count the tears I’ve cried
My tears will merge with the rain that has kissed the earth
My sorrow stayed even as the sun went down
And I’ll lie down without owning happiness
Please, don’t give me hope
Watch me as I fall from giving up…
Don’t let your heart ache because of me
Don’t let the voice of this hopeless person reach your ears,
Lay me down so I can heal
Let’s not keep any more secrets between us,
be it our personal problems or whatever problems we may have…
let’s face them together.
Zo… I find this so hard to tell you…
I told you, no more secrets.
What is it that you’re hiding from me?
I can’t tell you.
Why can’t you?
I can’t.
Please tell me, Beth.
Tell me.
Zo, I don’t have much time to live.
What are you saying?
I have cancer.
We received the news from my tests last week and its stage 4.
Zo, please forgive me.
I don’t want you to suffer because of my disease.
But I can’t do it… I can’t take it anymore, I need you.
I want you… I need you by my side…
One by one, you take everyone I love away from me…
Why Betsie?
Why her?
Please, God, don’t take her from me.
You’re home, dear.
I came home a while back.
Why do you look so unhappy?
It’s nothing, mom, I’m good.
Come, sit with me, dear.
I’m your mother and I know you well, so tell me, son.
Mom… Betsie has cancer.
I don’t know what I’m going to do.
I’m so sorry.
I’m helpless, mom.
Don’t worry, dear, everything will be okay.
Why does God give only to take it away?
Never say that again. God’s plan is always directed towards what’s best for us.
Nothing is meant to stay forever, everything has its time.
Rather than grieving for what is lost, we should be grateful for the brief moment that we had it.
Now go spend as much time as you can with Betsie, and don’t think about the rest, okay?
Is anyone home?
Oh? Come inside. Oi! This is a surprise.
What are you doing?
I was just cleaning the house.
You didn’t you tell me beforehand…
I want to show you something.
What is it?
We’re going to Europe?
Yes!
I promised you., didn’t I?
Promise
- Promise
Out of everybody, you’re the only one I want
Oh, it been you and only you
Let’s swear on our lives and promise to stay together
I love staying in your arms
If Pete and Mk were here, they’d chase each other by now.
Pete would be in some sort of accident by now.
And Dave? Did you guys talk?
Mmm.
Hmm, you need to be the bigger person in this situation. Talk to him when we go home, okay?
We vowed to never take back our promises
I don’t know.
It’ll all work out.
Hold my hand tight, never let go
We vowed to never take back our promises
Even when we’re lain side by side to return to earth
Together we’ll soar and find our place in the sky
Beth…
Mm?
Can you give me your phone?
Go stand over there, I’ll take your photo.
Beth… will you marry me?
Zodin… Are you sure you made the right decision?
I don’t know how we’ll meet in the sky…
so the time that we have now, I want to spend them with you.
Yeah… they say that everyone, even our loved ones roam the sky… So it’s also ours.
You won’t like heaven without me anyway.
You’re not trying to make me live long, aren’t you?
Hi, Zodin, I need to talk to Betsie’s family.
It’s just me today.
Can I talk to you regarding Betsie?
Of course.
We’re doing our best but we believe Betsie may not have much time left…
The cancer has spread extensively and has caused significant damage. Her condition is unpredictable, so you have to prepare yourself for the worst.
Make sure that she spend her remaining days filled with happiness.
Where did you go?
I went to the shop… how do you feel?
I’m fine...
Really?
Mm. But I’m so tired of being in the hospital.
Do you want ot get fresh air?
Mm.
Get enough rest first, and then we’ll go out.
I want to climb a mountain.
You want to climb a mountain?
Mm.
Which mountain do you want to go to?
A really nice mountain.
Take me there later, okay?
Do you feel peaceful? scared?
No, I’m not scared, but…
When I have to leave, I don’t want to see you in pain…
If our loved ones are hurt, the person who loves also gets hurt…
Zo…
Hmm?
I want you to be happy even when I leave…
besides, when our days on earth have drawn to a close, the sky is ours. I’ll wait for you.
Are you in touch with Dave?
He’s out of touch with everyone these days, wonder what’s wrong with him.
Yes, Zodin? Yeah… what?
Okay… all right.
Betsie’s condition got worse, we need to leave now.
Oh, really? Wait, let me just update Dave.
Yeah, hello?
Am I late?
Not late at all. How are you?
I’m good.
My sister told me to give this to you before she passed away.
Hello...
If you’ve watching this video, it means I would’ve passed away.
I wanted to make a short video before my disease eats me up...
Zodin, I told you not to be lonely and miserable. Look at your face now... I told you I can’t stand you being lonely...
but... whenever you miss me or want to talk to me or want to see my face...just look up at the sky... I’ll be up in the heavens that time... I’ll look over you from above...
Don’t feel alone... you have your friends with you, I’ll be here if you ever want to talk... all you have to do is look up... this is so hard...
Even the others... Dave, life is great isn’t it? Enjoy all you want but know that your friends love you so much...
Don’t take all the burden to yourself... please remember that your friends are like your family, you can confide in them
and I know how much you love them and need them... so... stick close to them...
Mk... look at your friends, none of them are happy...
and none of them will be happy without you, so keep on being the sunshine... it’s your responsibility now.
never forget that your friends are your family...
and finally, Pete, don’t think that I’ve missed you out, I didn’t forget you.
I know you don’t talk a lot but never forget how precious you are to your friends...
the four of you need each other so never turn your back on each other.
Zodin, everything that I had been though... you made me forget my worst memories by spending time with you... I’m so grateful.. but I’m sorry...
I wish I could stay with you forever... I wrote a song for you... and its in this pendrive... please listen to it and I hope you like it...
and... Zodin... even though our time was short, you’ve made it my heaven on earth and thank you for leaving me with no regrets... thank you for loving me, and you know that I love you too...
For tonight’s Thazual Award performance, we’ll call to the stage the youth sensation. They have been the chart toppers for quite a while
and they have left their marks not just in Mizoram but abroad as well, let’s call out The Hangout Boys. They’re dedicating this song to Betsie who had passed away.